one of the most important things you can
focus on is the nature of development
itself and the nature of your own
learning so learn about the nature of
learning scientifically but also learn
about your own unique learning needs and
patterns right so not everyone can sit
with a book for 45 minutes but they can
do 15 minutes get up staring space walk
around 15 minutes get up stand in space
walk around ready so you learn how you
work and a lot of research can help with
that things like the neuro hacker
resources all of these things should be
grist for that mill but one of the
things that you see with people who go
postconventional and kind of become self
actualize and move up to these higher
levels that they're very reflective
about their own learning they know how
they learn when they learn best I know
what excites them to know how to follow
investigative patterns independently and
so they're reflective and so they create
these virtuous cycles of learning for
themselves naturally
throughout life to watch the full
episode or to subscribe to the podcast
click the link in the description or
visit us at neuro hacker comm slash
collective insights to celebrate the
launch of this podcast we're giving away
a bunch of great prizes including a six
month subscription of qualia for details
on how to enter the contest go to neuro
hacker com